gospelminds.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Mp3 Download Gospelminds.com

Your privacy is critically important to us. If there is need for questions about our privacy policy, please contact us by email at support@gospelminds.com

It is Gospel Minds policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [www.gospelminds.com/](http://www.gospelminds.com/) (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or [“www.gospelminds.com/”)](http://www.gospelminds.com/). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information (PII) you may provide us through the Website.

We have adopted this privacy policy [(“Privacy Policy”)](https://gospelminds.com/gospel-minds-privacy-policy/) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the [**Terms and conditions**](https://gospelminds.com/terms-of-use/) posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

#### **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Gospel Minds collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Gospel Minds’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Gospel Minds’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Gospel Minds may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
Gospel Minds also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on [http://www.gospelminds.com/](https://web.facebook.com/gospelminds2017) blog posts. Gospel Minds only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Gospel Minds’s websites choose to interact with Gospel Minds in ways that require Gospel Minds to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Gospel Minds gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog post at <http://www.gospelminds.com/> to  email address.

#### **Security: Gospel Minds Privacy Policy**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### **Advertisements**

Currently no third party Ads on our website.  
**– Links To External Sites**  
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.  
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

#### **Aggregated Statistics**

Gospel Minds may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Gospel Minds may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Gospel Minds does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

Gospelminds may use cookies to provide a better experience for our users. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes, as well as for tracking information. You can set your browser to refuse cookies at any time, or alert you when they are being sent. [What Are Cookies?](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie)

#### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

#### **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Gospel Minds may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Gospel Minds’s sole discretion. Gospel Minds encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
